#### Contact

nichowards12@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nicole-howard-1383a057 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare Nursing ACLS

# **Nicole Howard**

Case Manager - Workers Compensation at ALARIS Group Inc Houston, Texas

## Summary

My name is Nicole Howard. I was born and raised in Houston, TX. I went to Texas Woman's University where I graduated in 2011 with my Bachelors of Science in Nursing. I was hired with Houston Methodist Hospital in 2011 worked in a general Med/Surg and IMU unit for over 3 years and then transferred to Houston Methodist Willowbrook hospital where I worked on a general med surg and cardiac unit. In 2015 i transitioned to a case management role and now am working in workers compensation.

## Experience

ALARIS Group Inc
Case Manager Workers Compensation
February 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months)

#### Anthem

RN Field Service Coordinator April 2015 - February 2019 (3 years 11 months) Houston, Texas

I am serving as a service coordinator/case manager for the TX Medicare Medicaid Program (dual demo) that is a pilot program in 4 counties in Texas.

The Methodist Hospital System
Registered Nurse
September 2011 - March 2015 (3 years 7 months)
Houston, Texas Area

I provide nursing care in a medical/surgical and intermediate (IMU) care unit, focusing mostly on the geriatric population.

Grace Care Center of Cypress Registered Nurse- Weekend Nurse Manager September 2012 - August 2013 (1 year) Cypress, Texas Provide and coordinate care for residents at Grace Care both on the rehabilitation and assisted living units.

## Education

University of Houston-Clear Lake

Master's in Healthcare Administration · (2012 - 2014)

Texas Woman's University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2009 - 2011)